<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fusaroli, R | ChrisCox</title>
    <link>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/author/fusaroli-r/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/author/fusaroli-r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Fusaroli, R</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/media/icon_hua2ec155b4296a9c9791d015323e16eb5_11927_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Fusaroli, R</title>
      <link>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/author/fusaroli-r/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bayesian meta-analysis of infants’ ability to perceive audio--visual congruence for speech</title>
      <link>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/publication/a_v_meta_analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/publication/a_v_meta_analysis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This paper quantifies the extent to which infants can perceive  audio–visual  congruence  for  speech  information  and  assesses  whether  this  ability  changes  with  native  language  exposure  over  time.  A  hierarchical  Bayesian  robust  regression  model  of  92  separate  effect  sizes  extracted from 24 studies indicates a moderate effect size in a positive direction (0.35, CI [0.21: 0.50]). This result suggests  that  infants  possess  a  robust  ability  to  detect  audio-visual  congruence  for  speech.  Moderator  analyses, moreover, suggest that infants’ audio–visual matching  ability  for  speech  emerges  at  an  early  point  in  the  process  of  language  acquisition  and  remains  stable  for  both native and non-native speech throughout early development.  A  sensitivity  analysis  of  the  meta-analytic data,  however,  indicates  that  a  moderate  publication  bias for significant results could shift the lower credible interval to include null effects. Based on these findings, we  outline  recommendations  for  new  lines  of  enquiry  and suggest ways to improve the replicability of results in future investigations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1111/infa.12436&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1111/infa.12436&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A systematic review and Bayesian meta-analysis of the development of turn taking in adult-child vocal interactions</title>
      <link>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/publication/tt_paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/publication/tt_paper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Background: Turn taking appears to be an almost universal phenomenon in communicative behavior and requires tight coordination between interlocutors. However, there is no current consensus on how and when infants develop the ability to take turns in vocal interactions and which mechanisms are involved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aim:  The current study aims at better understanding the current state of research on the development of turn-taking behaviors in human infants. In particular, we want to map the developmental trajectory of turn-taking abilities and identify key moderators affecting them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Method: We performed a systematic review and Bayesian multilevel meta-analysis of studies reporting response latencies in infant-adult dyadic interactions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Results: We found a poorly connected field (low rate of citations between papers), from which we identified 26 studies and 78 unique estimates of infant response latency. Infants display fast  response latencies at an early point in development, which gradually increase up to 40 months. Infants’ responses also appear to be strongly related to the pause duration of their adult conversational partners, and are slower in groups with atypical development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Conclusions: We identify current pitfalls and new directions of research. Specifically, we advocate for the development of shared longitudinal cross-linguistic corpora with turn-by-turn data and rich assessment of the infants&#39; linguistic and social development. We also recommend more explicit definition and testing of computational models of the mechanisms underlying turn-taking.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infant Development as Uncertainty Reduction: Bayesian Insights on Phonological Acquisition</title>
      <link>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/publication/bayesian_insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/publication/bayesian_insights/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bayesian accounts of development posit that infants form predictions about the causes of sensory signals in their environment and select actions that resolve the largest amount of uncertainty. This paper  considers  how  this  approach  to  infant  development  can  inform  and  unify  insights  from experimental  research  on  early  cognitive  development  and  language  acquisition.  In  order  to establish whether infants’ early inferential abilities conform to the basic assumptions of a Bayesian approach to cognition, we first conduct a systematic review of experimental studies on infants’ ability to form predictions about probabilistic contingencies. These studies provide evidence that infants  exhibit  sensitivity  to  the  probabilistic  structure  of  their surrounding  environment  and recruit  their  own  uncertainty  to  guide  their  exploration  of  information  in  the  world.  We  then demonstrate how these Bayesian computational principles may apply in the context of language acquisition  by  conducting  a  second  systematic  review  of  experiments  on the  facilitative  role  of infants’  vocal  production.  These  studies indicate  that  infants  are  more  likely  to  produce  and allocate attention to those speech sounds that best afford the opportunity to reduce prediction error over time. This paper demonstrates how Bayesian models of cognition can offer a unifying framework  to  advance  the  understanding  of  cognitive processes  in  early  development. This framework not only gives a larger perspective to current findings, but also provides conceptual tools to enable investigation of infants’ individual trajectories of behavioural change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://psyarxiv.com/ny6vj/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://psyarxiv.com/ny6vj/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
