<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2 | ChrisCox</title>
    <link>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/publication-type/2/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/publication-type/2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>2</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/media/icon_hua2ec155b4296a9c9791d015323e16eb5_11927_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>2</title>
      <link>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/publication-type/2/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bayesian meta-analysis of infants’ ability to perceive audio--visual congruence for speech</title>
      <link>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/publication/a_v_meta_analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/publication/a_v_meta_analysis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This paper quantifies the extent to which infants can perceive  audio–visual  congruence  for  speech  information  and  assesses  whether  this  ability  changes  with  native  language  exposure  over  time.  A  hierarchical  Bayesian  robust  regression  model  of  92  separate  effect  sizes  extracted from 24 studies indicates a moderate effect size in a positive direction (0.35, CI [0.21: 0.50]). This result suggests  that  infants  possess  a  robust  ability  to  detect  audio-visual  congruence  for  speech.  Moderator  analyses, moreover, suggest that infants’ audio–visual matching  ability  for  speech  emerges  at  an  early  point  in  the  process  of  language  acquisition  and  remains  stable  for  both native and non-native speech throughout early development.  A  sensitivity  analysis  of  the  meta-analytic data,  however,  indicates  that  a  moderate  publication  bias for significant results could shift the lower credible interval to include null effects. Based on these findings, we  outline  recommendations  for  new  lines  of  enquiry  and suggest ways to improve the replicability of results in future investigations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1111/infa.12436&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1111/infa.12436&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did I just do that?”—Six-month-olds learn the contingency between their vocalizations and a visual reward in 5 minutes</title>
      <link>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/publication/babbleapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/publication/babbleapp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It has been shown that infants can increase or modify a motorically available behavior such as sucking, kicking, arm waving, etc., in response to a positive visual reinforcement (e.g., DeCasper &amp;amp; Fifer, 1980; Millar, 1990; Rochat &amp;amp; Striano, 1999; Rovee-Collier, 1997; Watson &amp;amp; Ramey, 1972). We tested infants to determine if they would also change their vocal behavior in response to contingent feedback, which lacks the social, emotional, and auditory modeling typical of parent-child interaction. Here, we show that in a single five-minute session infants increase the rate of their vocalizations in order to control the appearance of colorful shapes on an iPad screen. This is the first experimental study to demonstrate that infants can rapidly learn to increase their vocalizations, when given positive reinforcement with no social element. This work sets the foundations for future studies into the causal relationship between the number of early vocalizations and the onset of words. In addition, there are potential clinical applications for reinforcing vocal practice in infant populations who are at risk for poor language skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1111/infa.12433&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1111/infa.12433&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying sources of variability in infancy research using the infant-directed-speech preference</title>
      <link>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/publication/manybabies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://4CCoxAU.github.io/website/publication/manybabies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Psychological scientists have become increasingly concerned with issues related to methodology and replicability, and infancy researchers in particular face specific challenges related to replicability: For example, high-powered studies are difficult to conduct, testing conditions vary across labs, and different labs have access to different infant populations. Addressing these concerns, we report on a large-scale, multisite study aimed at (a) assessing the overall replicability of a single theoretically important phenomenon and (b) examining methodological, cultural, and developmental moderators. We focus on infants’ preference for infant-directed speech (IDS) over adult-directed speech (ADS). Stimuli of mothers speaking to their infants and to an adult in North American English were created using seminaturalistic laboratory-based audio recordings. Infants’ relative preference for IDS and ADS was assessed across 67 laboratories in North America, Europe, Australia, and Asia using the three common methods for measuring infants’ discrimination (head-turn preference, central fixation, and eye tracking). The overall meta-analytic effect size (Cohen’s d) was 0.35, 95% confidence interval = [0.29, 0.42], which was reliably above zero but smaller than the meta-analytic mean computed from previous literature (0.67). The IDS preference was significantly stronger in older children, in those children for whom the stimuli matched their native language and dialect, and in data from labs using the head-turn preference procedure. Together, these findings replicate the IDS preference but suggest that its magnitude is modulated by development, native-language experience, and testing procedure.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
